(Sheldon:)It's yet another way
I'm exactly like Batman.
And for the record,
Jimmy wasn't the reason I wet the bed.
(Leonard:)That one has my mother
written all over it.
(Penny:)Anyway, I'm really sorry I made fun
of your stutter in high school.
(Bernadette:)You're doing great.
(Penny:)Uh-huh.
Oh, God, just finish the sentence.
Ah. Okay, well,
I'm sorry you feel that way.
(Penny:)Bye.
(Penny:)- No one wants to hear my apologies.
- Your mistake is doing it over the phone.
I mean, if they could look into your eyes,
they'd meIt.
(Bernadette:)It doesn't matter what you did
in the past. You're a good person.
Yeah, that's easy for you to say.
You weren't just called a "b-b-bitch."
Perhaps you could assuage your guiIt
through aItruism.